Zoos are really fun. They have a huge problem though:
Government meddling!
There's no reason visitors shouldn't be allowed to box a bear.
Fortunately, Planet Zoo takes place in an alternate world where everything is allowed.
Everything.
So today I will show you what a perfect zoo would look like in a utopia.
First we need to decide ticket price. It needs to scare off the wrong crowd.
Of whom do I speak?
Well, people tell you they love animals
-and then you ask them: "Okay, name 5 species in the Mungotinae subfamily."
(Crossarchus platycephalus, Crossarchus ansorgei, Crossarchus obscurus and Crossarchus alexandri
From what I found there isnt 5,
you're welcome)
And they shut up.
I would never allow fake fans in my park. So ticket prices will be $800.
So what should the park look like?
Umm... like...
LIKE THIS! With a tower of Animalon. It challenges the true devotion of animal lovers.
At the bottom you have terrible animals that need to be destroyed such as amphibians *hum hum*.
Then mediocre animals like ostriches.
Moving a little bit higher, lions.
But then... you reach the top.
And you aren't faced with an animal, you are faced with a superior being.
The Red Panda.
They will share divine wisdom to you moronic mortals.
Here is the perfect zoo.
The rating system for parks in this game goes from 1 to 5 stars, but I wouldn't be surprised if the game breaks and gives me 6 stars.
What do you mean 3½ stars?!
"Tickets are too expensive"?! "Education low"?!
Of course it's low, I expect people to know literally every fact about every animal before they come here.
Like how I expect my subscribers to know literally every pop culture reference in history.
I have never been this disrespected in my entire life. >:(
Damn you humans designed by people who can really design animals but clearly have never seen a human.
You think this zoo is bad? You have made a severe lapse in judgement, Elvin.
I'll show all of you. I shall create the worst zoo one could possibly imagine.
"Hi Kilian. Isn't the worst zoo just opening a lion's cage, letting them attack humans?"
No child. You wouldn't visit such a zoo. And if you did you could sue them, it's like 'skip it or pay a housing loan'.
That's like a 3 star zoo.
i'm talking about a place that is consistently bad. But not so bad that you can completely dismiss it.
A 'Zoo 76', if you will.
First we need to decide where to put it.
North Korea? Maybe the South Pole?
Maybe worse? (what?)
No. I know a small town in northern Ukraine called Pripyat looking to repair their amusement park.
We need a name that makes you go "ugh". Like...
'TikTok Zoo Challenge'.
Here we are!
This used to be a ghost town, now 50 people live here.
Perfect place for a resistance base, *hum hum*.
Time to start building. Let's begin by asking 'What is the worst thing about zoos?'
If you respond: "I'm a vegan and I have a lot of opinions on this subject."
That's the wrong answer. The real answer is-
-children.
By the park entrance a lot of zoos have their petting zoo for children.
We will too. But we will make it extremely expensive so no parents will pay the price.
Children, having no concept of expensive stuff, will whine that they didn't get to go for the rest of the visit.
Will there be any other animals at the start?
Yes. We'll have tigers! (Lions)
But you can barely see them behind the wind power plants.
We'll have a giraffe pen...
...No giraffe in it. (perfect)
But this first section of the zoo mostly has turtles.
6 turtle habitats. (more there should be more)
Some zoos have an aerial lift at the entrance, so shall we.
We'll call it the 'Great View Lift'.
The Great View is concrete.
Concrete and dirt.
And it's 2 hours.
But it's free.
After you're done with that you're probably starving.
"Kilian, what's the food like in the park? Lemme guess...
"Hawaiian Pizza only."
What, no.
Why would I have the same food as in the perfect park?
More on that in the upcoming video.
Also it's not so simple as just bad food.
You aren't seeing the possibilities, the artistry, the patterns, the equations.
The zoo will only have taco places serving large tacos.
With toppings of excessive amounts of salsa and jalapeños.
And now the cherry...
One toilet!
For 1000 visitors.
No...
Two!
But one will always be out of order.
We're not done yet.
The toilets will obviously cost money. But how much?
Not an exact number like a dollar, everyone has a dollar.
And it can't be too expensive, people will just roll their eyes and walk away.
The most soul-crushing sum...
-is 49¢ in exact change!
Now that our guests have emptied their pockets of all change, let me tell you a little secret.
This isn't just any old 'TikTok Zoo Challenge'.
This is 'TikTok Zoo Challenge World'.
We have several sections!
To get to them you have to climb stairs that just lead up and down.
And they are heated to 50 degrees [Celsius].
That's 122 Hamburger degrees.
But it's worth the climb because you get to enter
the bench-less Snail and Cockroach Park.
A section of the park that only has snails.
But snail habitats are expensive.
[They aren't actually] but I want money.
But the park is awful.What's something that can be awful but still make a lot of dosh?
Welcome to the section: 'Mobile Game Zoo'.
You can watch the animals, but the view is awful.
You can get a better view if you walk through these 7 gift shops.
We also have something similar to lootboxes.
Pick a train! You might get to see a peacock, maybe a cheetah, or the grand prize: a great panda.
Guess which one leads to the panda?
They all lead to spiders.
But speaking of mobile games, today's sponsor is:
RAID: Shadow Legends
Skillshare.
Wait, what?
It's an online learning service with thousands of courses, for example:
Productivity Masterclass.
Imagine if you signed up to box a bear.
You'd probably die instantly.
But maybe, if you were productive, coming up with strategies:
You would die later in the hospital.
If you click the link in the description you get 2 months for free. After that it's only $10 a month.
Premium membership gives you unlimited access to classes.
Maybe aliens take over the planet; the resistance is going to need productive people. *Hum hum*
Shillshare!
You can't predict the future, but you should prepare for literally everything possible.
The next section is 'Are they there or are they not?'
This is the section of the park where the habitats *might* be empty,
but like I think I see an animal over there... um, I'm not sure...
Child: "Dad, I wanted to see the lemurs."
Parent: "They aren't here right now honey."
Parent: "Park workers, we came all the way from distant place to see the lemurs."
Park worker: "They are sleeping, sir. Parent: "Well wake them up, I paid good money."
Park Worker: "Your family is the zoo attraction, sir."
*MmmHmm*
Finally you reach the gift shop section.
You hated your experience here, but the prices will be cheap. So you'll have to buy stuff.
And there will be signs everywhere that says:
"These things weren't ethically made in the slightest."
These adorable panda plushies that you have to have, one guy lost his eye making them.
And that was the day before his 7th birthday.
There we go, the worst zoo in existence!
.
..
...
Really getting annoyed with you, viewer.
I've tried to explain the situation, but the fact that you are still here means you aren't paying attention.
Do I have to spell out what I have been covertly trying to tell you?
Okay!
Maybe we need one more section!
Where humans are in the cages, and they're being watched by lizards because that's what's happening right now!
This planet is a giant zoo for the lizard people, but the resistance is strong!
[Breaching noises]
Ahh, and now they're here.
Come on you Cold-Bloods, I have a flamethrower!
[Sounds of battle]/[Alarm sounds]
Glory to Terra!
[Laser gun sounds]
Oh, you think you scare me? Well look what I have in my hand.
It's a cayenne taco! Everyone knows lizards are terrified of cayenne tacos.
Do not try to steal my Solarian pamphlets, you scaled bastard!